{
    "id": "770f0c14abd2475a9bf62f7ddddd3025",
    "title": "Nouns Worksheet",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We have received no …………………. from them.",
            "description": "Information is an uncountable noun it does not have a plural form.",
            "answers": [
                "information",
                "informations"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am selling my …………………….",
            "description": "Furniture does not have a plural form.",
            "answers": [
                "furniture",
                "furnitures"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You have got too much …………………….",
            "description": "Luggage does not have a plural form.",
            "answers": [
                "luggages",
                "luggage"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is collecting money for ………………………",
            "description": "The blind means all blind people. This expression cannot be used without 'the'.",
            "answers": [
                "blinds",
                "the blind",
                "the blinds"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There are still many ……………………. In the world.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "poor",
                "poors",
                "poor people"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I saw two ………………….. in the store.",
            "description": "Women is the standard expression. ",
            "answers": [
                "females",
                "women",
                "female"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The ……………………. are grazing.",
            "description": "Cattle is a plural noun.",
            "answers": [
                "cattle",
                "cattles"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He has a huge ……………………. of money.",
            "description": "Number is used with countable nouns use amount with money.",
            "answers": [
                "amount",
                "number",
                "quantity"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "A large …………………… of people want to buy cars.",
            "description": "Use number with plural nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "number",
                "amount",
                "people"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She has got lovely black …………………….",
            "description": "Hair is uncountable in English.",
            "answers": [
                "hair",
                "hairs",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The news …………………….. too good to be true.",
            "description": "News is uncountable and takes a singular verb.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you give me some …………………….?",
            "description": "Advice does not have a plural noun.",
            "answers": [
                "advice",
                "advices",
                "advise"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}